Nogizaka Distribution
For the first time
How do you feel about the first time you saw the opening of today's fun?
It was my first time.
I thought you did it all the time.
I was just checking.
You want me to do it? Like that.
I've never done it before.
That's how we're going to play today.
We're going to play together in Romatis World.
Yay!
I've always wanted to do that.
I'm so glad.
You don't get a chance to play with the members like this very often, do you?
That's right.
That's why I've been looking forward to it so much.
I've been looking forward to it, too.
You've been psyched?
I got mine last night.
I got it last night.
Wow, you're really into it.
Have you really played? Momotetsu?
I've never played World.
I've never played World, but I've played Peach Tennis.
My family plays it, and my friends play it, too.
Sounds tough.
You think so, don't you?
You know, the kind of guy who's always wearing a "Bomby" shirt.
Yeah, that's how I remember it.
Did you go hard today?
I'm already hungry and fired up.
Eneche?
I've come with the intention of eating.
I'm actually looking forward to the delivery.
I'm looking forward to it.
This place is going to be great. Let's use it without getting it dirty.
Today we're going to fight a three-year battle.
Den-chan and I will be working solo, since we're both experienced.
Two of you will be fighting as a team, and the fourth will be the computer.
There's a strong guy named Tetsuto Sakuma.
Let's beat him so we don't lose to him!
Let's do our best! Let's beat him!
Then let's get started.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's change our names.
I am...
Homio.
Do you have a name like that for the game?
I'm just wondering if you have one.
If I write it here, you'll know.
Hit me up for an online game or something.
Next.
What shall we do?
I'll take care of it.
Well, well, well... don't say it.
Tetsujin Sakuma...
What about Tetsujin Sakuma?
Change it?
I'll make it something cute.
I'm sure.
What do you think?
Tetsujin.
Tecchan?
He's so cute!
You're not going in, are you, Tecchan?
You're an iron man, right?
Tetsudou?
Iron Man?
"Iron Man" sounds strong.
Yes, he looks strong.
Iron King.
Let's go with "Iron King".
Done!
Amazing human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human human
It's a genre called "Sakuma-san"!
That's great!
The genre is Sakuma-san!
Wow!
He's riding a bear!
He's so cute!
What am I going to do?
Oh, my camera!
Let's put a bear on it!
Oh, it's so cute!
We can do that, too.
Okay, what should we do?
Maybe I'll make a turtle.
The colors don't match.
Pink and green.
I'll go with peach.
A pretty peach.
Let's go with peach.
They're yellow, so they'll go well together.
Certainly a turtle!
So cute!
Let's turn iron into tortoise
Certainly turn iron into tortoise
2 Currency surface... ahhh... nice familiarity... cute...
It's cute, but it's not that cute...
I wonder how it will turn out...
I wonder what's going to happen... what's going to happen... what's going to happen...
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good
I'm so happy, it's my first time in the world!
I'm so glad.
It's my first time, too.
I wish I could have done it.
The world's going to fly away.
You know what I mean? Tochi.
Yes, I do.
But I'm studying.
That's right.
Japan doesn't know either, right?
Japan doesn't know either.
Japan understands.
Because I like it.
I understand.
I know Mayu.
Mayu doesn't understand.
I understand.
Oh!
There it is, the usual character.
Oh, it's the usual character.
I wonder where he is.
I wonder where...
Oh, is it close?
Close.
I wonder if it's close.
Wow, I want to go there.
How do you get there?
I don't know, maybe...
You know, maybe...
I mean, maybe we should take a plane.
We'll fly.
Oh, I see.
Fifteen squares.
Back there.
Maybe we should stay with the cards.
Use the propeller cards.
Maybe we can get a six and a six or something.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
That's a good one.
It explains a lot.
It's a three-minute fold. You can use it three times.
Like that one, or the express card.
Seven.
Three times already.
That was fast.
We did it.
You're early.
I'm gonna buy all of them, or I'm gonna buy all of them.
I'll buy them all... or I'll buy them all... and if I get beat up, I'll get beat up... and if I don't get beat up, I won't get beat up...
I'm gonna get robbed.
I'd rather do propellers here...
I'd love to do propeller here.
Oh! We're in the same place!
Same place! But we can't afford it.
I'm buying.
You can go there, too?
Oh, yeah.
You can't afford it.
You want to take a look?
I can't afford one.
That's too bad.
That's great.
What am I going to do if I get stuck?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Something professional about this place.
Where is it? Downstairs. Close.
I need a card.
I'm gonna have to go. Just a little closer.
Oh, my God.
More money. Money's important.
It's a train bath, right?
You're all so close.
Oh, no, not really.
I didn't expect that.
Eight squares.
It's not like you can go around the whole place.
Yeah, but...
We have to go this way.
It's so far away.
It's just 8 squares.
I guess I'd better.
Ten.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me, but it's a huge mistake.
But it's going to grow. More money, more money, more money.
More money, more money, more money...
It's good, isn't it?
Left?
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm being bullied.
-I want you to stop right in front of me where there's traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic, traffic.
I'm going to change the card in the back of the car.
You're gonna change it to 40 million... and you're rich.
Oh, my God, there's so many of them.
Wow, there's a lot of stuff here.
A goody bag!
I bought a goody bag with cards in it...
It's fun to buy a goody bag, isn't it?
I wonder if I'm buying a grab bag
I'll get one later
I want to buy it
I'll get the iron.
I knew you'd pull it out
I'll...
I'll buy a lot.
Oh, shit.
But it's just normal... 7 squares.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'll see what I can do
I'll see what I can do with 80 minutes of my time.
I've got all this money, so I'll just go buy some more medicine... you never know where the extra income will come in today
I don't know where the extra money will come in today...
There's something here. Are you wearing it?
Unfortunately...
You're not going to change it, are you?
And there it is... five, five...
They're all in the same place.
If this is the Iron King, who are you going to make it for? People who don't have money.
Is that how it's going to be? No... they'll make it for me.
The Iron King!
Oh no! The Iron King is bad!
I'm screwed!
The Iron King! That's too much!
That's too much, Hanyu.
Hanyu, that's not quite what I meant.
That's not what I meant.
What?
There's too many eggs.
What? Why?
Why? Why?
Let's just...
Let's blame the Iron King for this.
Certainly.
You're right.
But he might dodge it.
Mr. Peach Butt!
Let's blow him away before he does that!
Let's blow her up!
If we blow her up...
What the hell!
You guys are in the same cell. That means it's dangerous.
But we're in the same square, so we'll be fine.
Are you sure?
I see.
Oh, my God!
Okay, now...
Where?
Bruenos Aires.
Far away.
Wow.
Where?
South America.
Ehhhh...
No, you're smart.
You know, that's what I'm talking about.
I thought so.
I'm surprised.
South America.
Bruenos Aires.
Oh, South America.
Bruenos ayrs.
It's strong! It's strong!
I'd like to hit it, but it's just like a pikan
I'd like to hit it, but it's the same as a pikan.
I'll just have to suck on the iron once and then fly away... there's no way I'm going to finish that quickly
I'll just use the dice.
But it's a waste to use it here.
We'll just roll the dice.
I'll just rub it on the Iron King, he's not the owner.
I'll eat this, John... but I can't afford it!
I'm going to put it on the Iron King... and see if it's mixed in with the dice.
I'm going to go for a fat card... and I hope there are more cookies in the second volume.
I've been looking all over for a cookie... a butter cookie!
I don't know... they're gone!
What cookies?
This is for you.
I'm so wasted. Oh, no, it's me.
I thought you were going to fly off the handle and I was looking away.
I thought it was going to be great!
I was so surprised I waited longer
Okamoto, Duty, Pfizer, Beer, Abe, Earl, and Orun
I'm not sure I'm a bje, but I'm a partial foot
In a short time, the ambition of the black flower
What, to Europe?
Burgundy and South America?
Lucky, lucky, lucky.
Oh, it's lucky.
Yay!
You're so close!
Let's go fly!
Let's go for a flying leap!
Let's do it!
I'm going!
Go ahead.
It's good, isn't it?
More!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
More, more, more.
Go, go, go.
What's that?
We did it.
Close, close, close.
Yes!
How do you not know it's close?
You can kind of tell, can't you?
I have a vague idea.
Where is it?
I don't know.
I'm sure.
I'm gonna use it.
I'm going to blow it again.
I'm gonna have so much fun, I'm gonna win.
Uh-oh. Faucer.
tee me
New Zealand's largest and top of the line G-type... I'm Alert!
Sits Lineios
Hey.
Was it that way? That way?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Flick.
But we're in a half-water red car.
Wisdom, spiritual, ambulator, we're getting close!
Chuck's ascending, synchronized Zaku-chan men
Down jumps steroid song pattern conhece
Wow, wow, wow!
Wow! My first time with this!
I'm sorry.
He said not to put up the house.
Wow, it's not good to eat.
There's another one.
I'll have another one.
You ate another one?
Yeah, fast.
That was fast.
Wow.
They're going round and round and round.
Here it is. Here it is.
What, me? That juice cell.
I wonder if I can make it. It's down there, isn't it?
Where is it? The card.
Denjan is playing here.
Thank you for watching.
I like the card.
Oh, Nishie. Nishie.
Can you tell which way is west?
Yes, yes, that's right.
This way, this way.
I knew it. I knew it.
I've learned. I can't... I can't... I can't... I have to dice it.
Too much dice, too much dice Too much dice, too much dice
It's a plus. Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good
Oh, well, well, well, well
There it is
I'm rich.
Okay, okay
I've got 300 million.
That's good.
I'll go get it.
I want to finish.
Oh, Carlon, that's nice.
I like that one.
That's a good one.
You can't do it.
I'll pack it in.
But it's close.
It's close.
Boo-boo. I love it.
Spray it on, Lettuce. They're all here, so cute.
It's in my mouth. It's full of pluses.
I've got a lot of pluses in my mouth, and I'm getting a lot of pluses, and I'm getting a lot of pluses, and I'm getting a lot of pluses, and I'm getting a lot of pluses.
I'm going to have fun with this game.
Maybe it's because I have money. People with money can afford it.
Nine more squares to go. I'll roll the dice.
But you're going to spend it? Let's use it.
Use it. I want a card.
I want a card. Nine, nine, nine, nine, nine.
Oh, that's cute. That's cute. That's cute.
What's on the property over here?
Uh, churrasco.
Oh, my God. Let's go to the property we want.
I'm sure there's something there. Let's get some stuff.
Let's buy it all.
I can't buy it, I can't buy it.
I can't buy it. I can't buy it.
It's too obvious.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I want 80% of what's in the restaurant.
And this.
And...
I don't know, I think I'll take the 8 pan.
Win!
Yay! That's good.
Okay.
I can't get to the finish line. It's so hard. I'm almost there.
Where's the move? It's me. I don't know.
I'm in Nedbourne. I'm in Australia.
Twenty-eight squares.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, that's good.
Meat pie.
I want steak.
I'm starving.
Eight.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's just go.
Oh, I think I'm going.
That's not easy.
But it's good, right?
It's good.
I got cards.
The card's good.
It's just one up here.
This one right here.
Gasoline?
There's a place where you can get a credit card.
I can't get rid of it.
I don't know what to do.
I want a card.
Yeah, I want a card.
Let's do cards, too.
I want a card.
I want my card!
Not good, more Liberal
Ki-chan's face is so bad, no, no, no, no, no!
You have a lot of hardware... wow, this is really good stuff!
Oh, I've got so many cards.
I've got four more squares. Can we do it?
Shall we do it? Shall we?
Let's do it.
Give me four. Give me four.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That's too close. Come on, guys. Come on, give me a shove.
But can you do it? Yeah, it's gonna work.
Oh, yeah!
We were so close. Go, go, go.
We did it!
I'm so happy. You did it!
But you know what? She can do it.
That's what I'm talking about!
Yay! 139! We're going to buy a lot of properties!
No, I don't mean "yay, yay!".
Here you go.
Ei!
Oh!
So close.
So close!
That's what I was aiming for.
Wow, that's what I'm talking about.
You're gonna get it.
I'll buy it, I'll buy it, I'll buy it.
Buy them all.
A billion.
A billion dollars!
Please don't do this.
Please don't do it.
Please stop.
Okay, I'll buy everything but this and the billion.
I'll buy everything but this and the billion.
Great.
I like that we can buy up to a billion.
That's nice.
We don't have any money.
I don't have any money.
5% of a billion?
I don't know.
Please don't.
I don't even know what I'm looking at.
I still have the first volume.
What? What? What?
What's going on?
It's my first time.
It's the first time you've ever done this.
What do you mean?
What am I supposed to do with this?
I don't know. It's so new.
Can I just turn it?
Turn it.
I didn't know that was possible.
You can't just go and leave.
I want to get to the finish line just in time.
I'll buy you a card.
I don't know if that's possible.
It's possible.
That's great!
I don't need it right now.
That's great.
What?
Oh, shit.
It's still okay.
It could be the baby.
Wait a minute.
Baby.
Oh!
Good boy.
Beautiful.
Cute.
She's got a lot of stuff.
I'll take it.
I'll take it. I'll take it.
What am I gonna do with it?
I'll use it later.
He's so cute.
Oh, my God. It's not that big of a deal.
How many squares did it say?
Twenty-nine.
You know, if you grab it, it's over.
If you put it on...
It'll fly!
I can't believe it!
That's great.
Oh, I think it's that way.
Oh, I'm done.
Bye-bye.
I don't think so.
You know, I think I might have a lot of birdies today.
Especially in Australia, really.
I know 50 people in the next town, so I wasn't playing ball.
I didn't have a ball.
Oh, man.
The Fesse is going to be awesome, and I'm half against it.
Why don't we just buy the same city?
I'm going to go to the west for two weeks
It says it's going to be far away.
If Haruka uses it...
That's not true!
No, it's not!
It's West, but it's not!
It's not Haruka!
No, it's not!
That pattern is going back, isn't it?
Let's go.
Hey...
Go back with this.
There we go.
It's coming back.
Please don't do this.
I'm done.
I'm done. I'm done.
Nothing happened.
Oh, God, I'm running out of cards.
Let's go.
All right, all right, all right.
Good luck with that.
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Where? America?
Shooter Gua, right?
Venezuela?
Venezuela.
Never heard of it.
I'm out.
Do you have any money?
You have money.
That's because you scored once.
I see.
30 is 30.
That's pretty close, isn't it?
Iron?
Iron? Oh, that's us.
Yeah, that's us.
I guess we're just gonna have to go with the norm.
What? I mean...
It's the only way to go.
I don't like the idea of jumping through hoops for three years.
I still have it.
I want a card.
Six.
Where? Which way? This way?
Down this way, I think.
Yeah, but it's red.
It's all red.
Down here.
Or you could buy a place.
Cards.
You could get a monopoly.
I've got a lot of money for exclusives, so...
He's got money for a place to stay.
Where do you want to go?
This is the silent one in Bure that I was telling you about.
Marci? Marci, open up.
You want to try this place?
Eight sandwiches and closing.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Delicious.
Invigorating.
2.2 billion.
Emi wants some too.
Can we buy all that stuff you just bought?
We can buy it all.
I'll give you 6,000 yen.
Come on, let's go here.
Six thousand!
I've spent all this money and I still have 4 more.
You bought 800 million? Yeah, that's right. That's great.
Please, please, please, please let us finish.
Yay!
Is this a German story?
It was me.
But it's pretty much just eight squares.
Oh, I see... I see... I'm a little far away.
I don't know.
The best of the best.
Ah! Mr. Deng!
Mr. Deng.
Oh, well, she's a baby.
Maybe Den-san will stay nearby.
I wonder where we'll be next.
I don't know where I'm going to be.
Where was I, Mr. Deng?
Oh, my God! Suddenly?
Kyoto!
That's a long way from here.
Wow, and I just finished jumping through hoops.
You just grabbed it, didn't you?
Oh, you won.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Wow, subtle.
Which one?
I want a card.
Oh, coffee.
Yum, yum, yum.
It's so good, isn't it?
It's gone so fast.
Want some? Want some?
Want some? I'd like to.
Drink? Can I have a baro?
Ah! Propeller.
You with me? I'm with you.
I don't have any money.
That's not good...
I don't want Tetsuo to get ahead of me.
But Tetsuo's got 500,000 yen too.
Tonga has a lot of cards...
Here we go again!
Ugh! This is a little disgusting.
He's a jerk...
They're gonna take it, aren't they? The one I want.
Oh, no!
You want to blow it?
Can you fly?
What? I was just doing that.
Yum! It's been a while since I've had one of these.
I'll let you use the malosie.
Blow it up! Go, go, go, go, go!
Japan! Japan! Japan! Japan! Japan! Japan! Japan! Japan!
No! No!
But where... where... where did we go?
But do we go to number 4?
We're already down there.
We can still fly.
Let's go again.
Where's this?
We're a long way from here.
Maybe we've gone too far.
But it's good... 51 squares.
Go!
Wow!
That sucks! That sucks.
Uh, to the airport.
Airport.
It's so far away.
Far.
Two.
Seven.
I'm so happy for you.
Yes, I did.
Yes, ma'am.
So, where's the right way to go?
We're gonna have to cross the ocean.
Is this it?
This is it?
Yeah, this is good.
That's 100% good.
Thank you.
Isn't the jet card good?
You're gonna do that for me?
Oh, no?
They just took my money?
Thank you. Thank you.
Angel.
They took my money.
They took about 18 million.
I lost the money.
Booth, I mean... oh, he did it to himself.
Yeah, that's a good one, Ty Traylor.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to take a lot of money, and I'm not going to do anything about it.
I'm going to do it on the route, so it'd be nice if you could put it on the bus, that's for sure.
I'm sure you're right.
I'm not back yet.
I wish you'd go back for more.
I want more!
More, more, more.
Much, much, much more.
That's so good.
It's getting closer. It's getting closer.
Adults are on us, too.
They're coming.
That's good.
I don't like it.
This is the one you can leave.
Yeah!
Oh, there's 11.
It's close!
That's good, right?
But there's 30 more.
Oh, no, wait.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh, thank God. Thank God.
Watch out, watch out.
I know I'm late, but I'm sick.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, now.
Baby, you're so cute.
Oh, baby, you're so cute.
I got two first places.
I think you mean this way. I guess so.
Shortest route. Wow, not so good.
This one's better.
I bought one of these and now here it is.
I can't change it anymore.
Oh, it's back.
Oh, no, it's back.
It was so cute.
Central Grand Building
Natsumi Natsumi and her mother Éric started the day with a möglich time, using their own things too!
You have to go see it, it's upsk!
And Yoongi sang fre д!
No, really!
Oh!
That's great!
He's buying a lot of properties.
Yes, I know.
You're the Specially Selected One.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm at the bottom of the list.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
When did this happen?
I don't know. I don't remember.
Oh, my God.
What's this?
I'm Yamashita.
Former president.
How stable is it?
Good company.
Lead the way.
Thank you.
You look great.
Dinner's here!
Chicken... our favorite... chicken... it's a delight, isn't it?
What's with the sweet potato balls?
I'm sure the sweet stuff will go down a treat... as we eat it.
I'm sure he's in the mood for a sleepover tonight.
I'm sure Kakuma's eating it.
I'm over here. It's this way.
Raren 악 role is too easy
Where's this time ee?
I think so...
Kyone
He's also a cerca for the convenience of the denpa.
I'm 100 times more interested in the face of the crest, etc.
Let's move on to Lopez's combustion!
4, stop it!
Oh, okay.
Here you go.
Is it cool?
I thought you didn't have the strength for the media.
I'm not a media guy, but you are.
And I'm glad I ate there, because I'm going to relocate to Cheeki for a big year of treatment!
By Strike
İşık around även ah!
İşık
This
Well wow yay 5 times more!
That's great!
I got a little bit more.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The hot chicken place was pretty good.
Goal, goal, goal.
What's an "Acky"?
He's so cute! I'm 16, but it's true.
Here you go...
I'm sorry, it's so rare...
It's cold this time of year, so... delicious sweet potatoes... once again... yummy!
Clothes, a little more...
I'm sorry, but...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry...
I can't get them to go in like this...
Delicious!
Full.
Eleven more questions.
The daikon radish looks good.
Where is it?
America.
Wow! Looks delicious!
Can we put this here too?
If you spill the juice...
Put it on.
Good job!
Three sheets again.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
You're a keeper.
You're gonna make me draw straws.
Good night.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, it's so expensive here.
They're all gone. Anything you say will be your main course.
Oh, I'm in the middle of something. Please call me when it changes.
There's a lot of buying going on.
You really don't have any cards.
We don't have any cards.
I can't remember the last time we stopped at a card square.
I want a card.
Here.
This one.
It's all we have.
Can we get on the boat?
No, thanks.
This one?
That's it.
I forgot where we're going.
Thank you very much.
What what what what?
Bookmark card
I wonder if I can bookmark it.
I don't know, let's look at it later.
what am I doing here all the time?
hmm
ENCOURAGES
Yum! Delicious!
This is the world.
Can you
Yup.
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Thank you for watching.
Oh, man.
I'd ball first, but...
Oh, 50,000.
But I'm with Jen.
Ball out, please.
I can do it.
Wow.
Again.
That was right in front of you.
Oh, my gosh.
There it is.
I'm the farthest away.
I know.
We made it! We made it to Kyoto!
You're almost home!
Almost.
Hello!
Yay!
Wow!
You're rich.
Yes, I am.
Yes, sir.
We're not doing this in Japan.
Wow, far away!
Far away again!
Everyone's far away!
Wow, that's really great!
I don't know if I can do this.
It's so good!
It's really good!
I can't believe it's Nintendo! This is a new product!
It was nothing! A game developer!
What should I do, buy it, buy it, buy it!
I'll buy the Kanji T-shirt shop too...
20% of 1 billion...
200 million.
What's 100 million?
Is there ever a boom time?
There might be.
What do you do with these types of places?
Buy it. Buy it.
Because Kiyoko's still here.
It's better not to have it.
You don't want to lose the money when you get the bombey, right?
No way.
You don't look like you're about to spill it.
I'm lost.
You're always lost.
You're taking it, right? No, I'm not taking it.
It's gonna spill. I'm sure of it.
I'm gonna put it on a plate.
Oh, thank you.
That's the best one right there.
Can you put them together?
It's like this. It's like this right here.
Would you put that in there?
It's like a bet.
Thank you very much.
I just wanted to show you something.
This is what it's all about, isn't it?
It's called "comorejuby.
Oh, it's delicious.
Yummy?
This way? This way?
Yeah, this way.
I can't go that far.
Which way should I go?
This way?
Where are you?
Where did you just go?
Oh, this one.
I guess it's better on the left, huh?
Is it better this way?
It's not that far.
Let's see the fastest route.
R?
That's all I see.
I'm going to try this. I'm going away.
I don't know, maybe it's better this way.
Maybe we should spend the money.
I have a lot of money.
I've got a lot of money.
I'm your father. I'm the one who's going to move you.
I think I'll just stay here for a minute.
Oh, my God.
I forgot we're here.
Oh, my God, I forgot.
Oh, no, no, no, baby girl.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! We're all passing each other.
I'm scared.
The world's gone dark.
It's like the pre-cure.
It's true.
Everyone's passing each other.
With out-of-sync girls.
No one's acting weird.
They hate me.
They hate me
How do you like it?
How's it going?
Is it bad?
Which way did this go?
Oh, it went that way.
I don't know what to do.
King Bongie.
Oh, shit.
Can't you tell?
King Bongie.
I don't know when it's coming.
I don't think so.
Go east.
I like the Iron King card.
I want an Iron King card.
Aren't we all about the same?
You're all pretty far away.
I don't have one card.
It's great when you use it on the property.
If I use it here, it'll be in Kyoto.
I'm going the other way now, so it's okay to put it here.
It's right in the middle, so it's good... and it's also good.
I've got a minute each, but I can't stay here...
You can live here if you want
Lucky you... don't stop at the stars.
Buy lots of cards... but not too many.
I'll have 900 million. I'll be fine.
You know what I'm talking about... a couple of cards...
I want this one.
What's the perfect card?
It's a card that gets us close to where we want to go.
Flower bowl. It means we can make it to the festival.
Like this one?
Like this one.
We can go right on top of each other, or we can go as close as we can.
What do we do?
I'll keep one of the special ones.
What do you think? Too expensive?
But I'll buy another one of these.
I've never had a card for these before.
It's different when you have money.
I'll buy a lot of snacks.
I like money.
I'm jealous.
You want to buy until it's 700 million?
Let's buy another one.
How many did you buy?
Okay, okay.
You bought about five?
I got four or five.
That's good.
We're gonna run out.
Oh, my God, it's huge.
I don't even have the cards from the spell.
It's gonna blow.
Go, go, go. Take the demon with you.
Giddyup, giddyup, giddyup.
What? Is that good?
It's definitely out and about, so...
Looks good.
What? It's good.
Oh, wait, that's close.
Oh, no.
It exploded.
Not the money... the money.
All the cards and stuff, it's gone.
KingMombie.
Wow.
Terrifying.
Red eyes
Four billion yen.
You don't have that much.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
You're lying.
Wouldn't it be faster to automate?
Sure would.
Sad music.
Meat Pie Specialty
My house.
Oh, my God!
It's so close!
So close!
Scary King Bomby!
Please put one on everyone's house!
I don't want to get too close.
Oh, man.
Where is it?
Oh, right.
Oh, shit.
That's the furthest I've ever been.
We have to use it all.
Do you have a card?
No, we don't.
Almost none.
But I only have two.
Oh, my God.
I didn't know Fight Bomby was this scary.
Oh, my God, what am I going to do?
I'll go.
Well...
Let's go east.
Oh, no, it's gone.
What's that? Much better.
Much, much, much.
What? Isn't it far?
It's a long way.
Oh, God.
I give up.
Good night.
September.
Sixty-five squares.
Lots of squares.
A lot of squares.
Is it good?
Let's use it all.
Give me a good boy.
It's okay.
Which way do you want to go?
Down?
Down.
I think we should go down.
It's the quickest way down.
I'm here.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no!
I don't speak English, but I'll go this way...
I'll go this way, I'll go this way, I'll go this way!
It's going through there!
I can't hear you, so I'm going this way.
I'll go through there.
I'm not going to be able to fly away... because I've done this... and I can't go any further... and I know I don't have two minutes... so I'm not going to be able to go any further...
No, I don't.
I'm not going to go back.
I'm not sure I can do this... and I know I don't have two minutes...
I'm not sure if it's the non-flying one or the flying one, but you have to come around from the other side.
If it's the non-flying one, you have to come around from the other side, you know.
The boat... the boat...
So it's this way.
Yeah. - Yeah, no.
No.
What's that? I wonder where we stopped to look earlier.
It's okay.
From the boat.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I'm going to go.
Yeah, it's blue. Where's the blue?
Where's the blue?
Oh, there's more.
Blue.
I don't care if they give me more money, it doesn't mean anything.
I'm getting it now...
Wow, that's great, but...
I'll get it now!
Asooran
I'll take care of the boo-boo card
I don't think he's following me
I want you to get a big roll of the dice
I want you to pull it out
Where am I going?
Wow, what should I do?
Melon roll.
It's a little peaceful.
I'm in a melon roll.
I'm a melon roll.
I wish I wasn't a King Bomby
Cards.
Have you seen the Iron King?
Where is the Iron King?
How are you?
I want you to tell me about the Tetsuou.
What's this?
Who's the No. 1?
You're doing it all by yourself.
That's great.
Looks like fun.
Dangerous.